Guide to the University of Chicago Library Office of the Director, Zella Allen Dixson, Records 1892-1910
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Administration
  - Correspondence, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Appropriations and expenditures, 1892-1908 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Decennial Publications, distribution, United States (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Decennial Publications, distribution, foreign (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Decennial Publications, distribution, mathematical and biological series only (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Departmental libraries, Superintendent, duties of, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Departmental libraries, miscellaneous records, 1907 and undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Fines received, 1893-1898 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Fire insurance, 1893, 1909, and undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Harper Memorial Fund, correspondence, 1906-1907 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Harper Memorial Fund, list of subscribers (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Loan Department, 1895-1900 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Missing books, 1895-1897 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Staff, departmental advisers and attendants, 1895-1897 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Staff, employment applications, 1892-1898 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Staff, employment applications, 1899-1905 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Staff, employment applications, 1906-1909 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Series II: Accessions
  - Accession reports, 1897-1910 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Accession reports, 1904-1910 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Accession Books 1-10000 (Baptist Union Theological Seminary) (Volume 1)
  - Accession Books, 10001-20000 (Volume 2)
  - Accession Books, 20001-30000 (Volume 3)
  - Accession Books, 30001-40000 (Volume 4)
  - Accession Books, 40001-50000 (Volume 5)
  - Accession Books, 50001-60000 (Volume 6)
  - Accession Books, 60001-70000 (Volume 7)
  - Accession Books, 70001-80000 (Volume 8)
  - Accession Books, 80001-90000 (Volume 9)
  - Accession Books, 90001-100000 (Volume 10)
  - Accession Books, 100001-110000 (Volume 11)
  - Accession Books, 110001-120000 (Volume 12)
  - Accession Books, 120001-130000 (Volume 13)
  - Accession Books, 130001-140000 (Volume 14)
  - Accession Books, 140001-150000 (Volume 15)
  - Accession Books, 150001-160000 (Volume 16)
  - Accession Books, 160001-170000 (Volume 17)
  - Accession Books, 170001-180000 (Volume 18)
  - Accession Books, 180001-190000 (Volume 19)
  - Accession Books, 190001-200000 (Volume 20)
  - Accession Books, 200001-210000 (Volume 21)
  - Accession Books, 210001-220000 (Volume 22)
  - Accession Books, 220001-230000 (Bernays Library) (Volume 23)
  - Accession Books, 230001-240000 (Volume 24)
  - Accession Books, 240001-250000 (Volume 25)
  - Accession Books, 250001-260000 (Volume 26)
  - Accession Books, 260001-270000 (Volume 27)
  - Accession Books, 270001-280000 (Volume 28)
  - Accession Books, 280001-290000 (Volume 29)
  - Accession Books, 290001-300000 (Law School) (Volume 30)
  - Accession Books, 300001-310000 (Volume 31)
  - Accession Books, 310001-320000 (Volume 32)
  - Lists of books purchased or suggested for purchase, faculty (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Lists of books purchased or suggested for purchase, departments (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lists of books purchased or suggested for purchase, Morgan Park Academy (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Lists of books purchased or suggested for purchase, General Library, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lists of books purchased or suggested for purchase, General Library, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Lists of books purchased or suggested for purchase, General Library, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lists of books purchased or suggested for purchase, General Library, 1898-1903 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lists of books purchased or suggested for purchase, General Library, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Berlin Collection, correspondence, 1891-1895 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Berlin Collection, sets and serial publications (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Berlin Collection, duplicates in General Library (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Durrett collection, "The Durrett Collection, Now in the Library of the University of Chicago," by Edward A. Henry, galley proofs, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Law Library, "Statement Regarding Law Book Buying," undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gift reports, 1893-1910 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Gifts accessioning procedures, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1896-1909 and undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Regulations governing submission and publication of theses, 1902-1909 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Institutions receiving U of C theses, 1906, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - "Memorandum on Theses and Programs of Foreign Universities in the U. of C. Library," undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Ph.D. theses received, 1894-1909 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Ph.D. theses not received, 1895-1910 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Master's theses not received, 1894-1910 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Series III: Classification
  - U of C (Dewey) classification schedules, 020-199 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - U of C (Dewey) classification schedules, 200-299.992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - U of C (Dewey) classification schedules, 348-547 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - U of C (Dewey) classification schedules, 572-581 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - U of C (Dewey) classification schedules, 610-615 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - U of C (Dewey) classification schedules, 620-779 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - U of C (Dewey) classification schedules, 839-921 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - John Crerar Library classification schedule, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Schwartz Classification (1871-1872) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified "Philosophy" schedule, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Series IV: Extension Libraries
  - Correspondence, 1893-1895 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1896-1897 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1898-1899 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1901-1902 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Report of Traveling Libraries, 1903, 1908, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Accession book, 1896-1903 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Accession book, 1903-1910 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Invoice lists, 1903-1904 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Invoice lists, 1904-1905 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Invoice lists, 1905-1906 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - List of Department of Religion books used, 1893-1894 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Rules and miscellaneous charging lists, 1898 and undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Series V: Equipment and Supplies
  - Advertising brochures, bookcases (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Advertising brochures, shelving and furniture (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Advertising brochures, shelving and furniture (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Advertising brochures, office supplies (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series VI: Scrapbooks
  - University of Chicago Library, General historical (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Library, Official publications (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Library, University Extension traveling libraries (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Arkansas, Conway, Hendrix College Library (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - California, Los Angeles, Redlands, and Riverside Public Libraries (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - California, Mount Hamilton, Lick Observatory Library (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - California, Pasadena Public Library (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - California, Sacramento Public Library (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - California, San Diego Public Library (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - California, San Francisco, Sutro Library (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Colorado, Denver Public Library (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut, Bridgeport Public Library (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Illinois, Bloomington, Withers Public Library (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Illinois, Champaign-Urbana, University of Illinois Library (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Illinois, Chicago, All Souls Church Library (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Illinois, Chicago, Armour Institute of Technology Library (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Illinois, Chicago, Art Institute Library (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Illinois, Chicago, Chicago Normal School Library (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Illinois, Chicago, Field Columbian Museum Library (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Illinois, Chicago, John Crerar Library (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Illinois, Chicago, Lewis Institute Library (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Illinois, Chicago, McCormick Theological Seminary Library (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Illinois, Chicago, Newberry Library (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Illinois, Chicago, Public Library (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Illinois, Evanston, Northwestern University Library (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Illinois, Evanston, Public Library (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Illinois, Oak Park, Scoville Institute (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Illinois, Peoria Public Library (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Illinois, Sycamore Public Library (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Iowa, Cedar Rapids Public Library (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Kansas, Lawrence, University of Kansas, Spooner Library (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Kansas, Ottawa Library Association (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Kansas, Topeka, Kansas State Historical Society (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Massachusetts, Northampton, Smith College Library (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Massachusetts, Salem, Essex Institute (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Missouri, St. Louis, Mercantile Library (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - New York, Albany, New York State Library (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - New York, Brooklyn, Pratt Institute Free Library (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - New York, Hamilton, Colgate University Library (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - New York, New York Public Library (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Ohio, Cleveland, Case Library (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Ohio, Cleveland, Public Library (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Ohio, Dayton Public Library (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania, Braddock, Carnegie Free Library (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Scotland, Glasgow University Library (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Wisconsin, Milwaukee Public Library (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous sample gift acknowledgements used at other libraries (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Series VII: Associations and Conferences
  - American Library Association (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Chicago Library Club (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Illinois State Library Association (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - International Library Conference, Second, London, 1897 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Missouri State Library Association, Trans-Mississippi Library Congress, Omaha, 1898 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Wisconsin State Library Association (Box 12, Folder 18)